

CURICULUM VITAE OBENG JEFFREY

PERSONAL OBJECTIVE

My goal as an IT Manager is to apply my in-depth knowledge in hardware and software applications and develop IT solutions to maintain continuity and efficiency of work in the organization. Equipped with solid background in systems installation, IT repair and replacement, troubleshooting and patching, I am positive that this objective can be achieved.

My six years' experience in different companies has enhanced my skills and broadened my understanding in supporting various computer systems and networks. I am a cisco certified network associate and also very knowledgeable in using different windows server systems, Active Directories and know how to manipulate subnets and firewalls.

CONTACT



stunite69@@gmail.com



+233-24-773-9288



Obuasi, Ashanti Region



https://jeffreyobeng.netlify.app/

HOBBIE







Music



EDUCATION

Presbyterian University College

Bachelor in Information Technology 2018-2021

NIIT University College

Professional Diploma in Information Technology (Networking Engineering) September 2013 – February 2016

OTHER QUALIFICATIONS

♦ Cisco CCNA 200-301 - CERTIFIED

GOOGLE IT - CERTIFIED

- ❖ Google IT Support
- Data Analytics
- IT Automation with Python

UDEMY CERTIFICATES

- ❖After Effects CC 2020
- ❖ Automate the Boring Stuff with Python Programming
- ❖Cisco CCNA Packet Tracer Ultimate Lab 200-301
- CompTIA A+ Certification (220-1002)
- ❖Kali Linux
- ❖Java: Build Desktop & Android Mobile Apps
- ❖Social engineering
- Linux Administration Bootcamp
- ❖The Complete 2021 Web development Bootcamp
- ❖The Complete JavaScript Course 2021
- ♦ Web Server IIS Mastery Course
- ❖ Virtual Private Network (VPN)
- ❖Windows Server 2012 System Administration
- ♦ Windows Server 2019





SKILLS PROFILE

- ♦In Depth knowledge of Windows, Mac and Linux Desktop systems, including installation, patching, troubleshooting and hardware replacement.
- ♦ Strong Knowledge of Active directory, group policy, Exchange 2010, SIMS, MS SQL 2008.
- Excellent working knowledge of Windows XP and Windows 7, Windows 2003/2008 Server, Terminal Services, Active Directory, IPSEC and SSL VPN, active directory, Exchange 2010 and VMware administration.
- ❖Strong ability to communicate technical information to non-technical Staff.
- Ability to conduct research into a wide range of computing issues.
- Ability to work as part of a team and communicate with staff at all levels

RELEVANT WORK EXPERIENCE

IT Support Officer

Obuasi Municipal Assembly

November 2018 - 2022

Supported and maintained the Company's IT systems including desktop provision, network infrastructure, and associated software and business applications.

Updates the register of IT assets and contributed to audits of IT licensing arrangements.

Coordinated IT equipment bookings and maintained equipment in a suitable condition for loan.

Advised staff and Members on their use of standard IT applications. Monitored system alerts and reports on servers and reported problems to the concerned IT Team Leader.

Updating OMA website.

Handled server shutdowns and restored service according to documented procedures.

IT Officer

Obuasi Municipal Library – Obuasi August 2016 – September 2017

- Monitored new IT developments and
- Supported the various systems and software packages currently in use.
- Provided a capability to tailor and customise functions and applications to improve work practices.

- Maintained all hardware, software, applications and interfaces.
- Contributed to the proper installation, maintenance and disposal of desktop computers and printers.

IT OFFICER COCOBOD (QCC) – OBUASI

2021 - 2022

- Monitored new IT developments
- Supported the various systems and software packages currently in use.
- Provided a capability to tailor and customise functions and applications to improve work practices.
- Maintained all hardware, software, applications and interfaces.
- Contributed to the proper installation, maintenance and disposal of desktop computers and printers.
- Train students and other registered member at the library
- **E-Learning Tutor and provide assistance to clients when needed.**

IT Technician / Tutor

Emmreg Computer Solution October 2015 – September 2016

REFERENCES

OBUASI MUNICIPAL ASSEMBLY

Mr. Kester Gyedu Dente Administrator 0243240242

OMA-MIT

Mr. Salifu Amidu, Assistant Programmer Obuasi Municipal Assembly Mobile: 0249163041

OMA-Library

Mr. Philip Asamoah, Director Obuasi Municipal Assembly 0209104663 / 0242689107

